Guide to the American Jewish Society for Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, Circa 1950s-2008; Accession 2009-M-004
  - Project files
    - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8-17)
    - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18-30)
    - 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
    - 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13-25)
    - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26-36)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1-9)
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10-22)
    - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1-11)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12-21)
    - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 22-30)
    - 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1-11)
    - 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12-16)
    - 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 2008 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
  - Photographs
    - 1950s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - 1954 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1957 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
    - 1964 (Box 6, Folder 15-18)
    - 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20-23)
    - 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24-27)
    - 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - 1970s (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30-34)
    - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35-40)
    - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41-44)
    - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 45-47)
    - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 1985 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
    - 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
    - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
    - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10-13)
    - 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
    - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16-18)
    - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20-22)
    - 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
    - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 25-29)
    - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
    - 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
    - 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5-8)
    - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
    - 2003 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
    - 2004 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
    - 2005 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
    - Undated and unidentified (Box 8, Folder 19-27)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - KGNS-TV, Channel 8, Laredo, Texas, 1988; 1 commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Channel 7, Amarillo, Texas, Undated; 1 commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Channel 10, Amarillo, Texas, Undated; 1 commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of founding of AJSS, Undated; 1 (Box 12)
    - Wilson, Daniel, A Summer of Caring, 1974; 1 commercially produced film reel (16mm) (Box 13)